The non-human part of you is about to lose all control.
They suspect it's magic that the humans have discovered
a forbidden enchantment that could destroy the world.
They called it Seraph of the End, I feel.
Snap out of it! Please, you!
And so it begins.
You! Stop it! Please, you have to!
For all of us are going to die!
Come back to us!
It's been five days. What the hell did you do to him?
What would you do to ensure the future of humanity?
How can we survive in this ruined world?
More importantly, how do we completely eradicate the vampires?
A human victory will require sacrifice.
As usual, the humans' lust for power is out of control.
And we vampires are so arrogant that we take things too lightly.
Wouldn't you agree with me?
The End
Lend me your power, Mahiru.
Go ahead and kill me. No one would blame you.
Don't mock me. You could dodge if you wanted.
I wouldn't mind if you were the one who took my life.
Looking for atonement?
Sorry, but you're going to have to live with your mistakes, sir.
My sister Mahiru loved you, Lieutenant Colonel.
But she was possessed by a demon. Passion consumed her.
And then you...
That's right.
I killed your sister.
But Mahiru didn't leave this world.
She became something else.
You used her to create your cursed gear and betray the Hiragi family.
You're possessed by my sister.
Is that why you're trying to manipulate you?
Because my sister is telling you to?
What's your endgame with him?
Lieutenant Colonel, if you're going to end up hurting you, even a bit, then I must humbly ask you to stop.
Why? Don't tell me you've fallen for that idiotic kid.
It's true that your sister is in here.
But I am the one who's in control.
I'm not possessed by her.
Would you even know if she had you?
I don't care whether you believe me or not.
You're always here lately.
What are you reading?
You scared me, Shinoa.
Aren't you still supposed to be on bed rest and recovering?
I was going nuts in that bed.
Besides, I feel totally fine now.
The doctors will decide when you're back in fighting shape.
Besides...
What is it?
Nothing. Forget it.
Wait, you're not really reading this, are you?
I bet you're hiding porn in here.
Hey, give that back.
Come on.
Where'd you hide it?
Jeez.
Tell me.
Do you want to turn Mika back into a human being?
If that's the case, I might have some helpful information.
Huh?
Do you want to hear it?
Yeah, I do.
Aw, you're always so cute and obedient whenever you want something.
Hey, shut up! Just tell me what you know, okay?
First of all, it's pretty rare that a human is turned into a vampire.
The bloodsuckers like to keep their ranks tight and their numbers small.
More importantly, within vampire society, the nobles are the only ones who have the authority to turn a human.
Wait, so it wasn't random that Mika was turned? He was chosen?
Can you think of a noble who might have picked him?
Yeah, maybe.
You know, it's our duty to destroy vampires. All of them.
Not him.
I thought Mika was dead.
But he's alive and that's enough.
Tell me, Shinoa.
Do you have any idea how to turn a vampire back into a human?
I see.
Well, now what?
I don't think that I've ever seen you look so serious before you.
It's almost like you found a whole new reason to live.
Special Private Yuichiro Hyakuya. Report to the First Office immediately.
I wonder what Gurren wants now.
No. It's probably the Hiiragi family who summoned you.
Hold on, the Hiiragi family? You mean the leaders of the demon company that got Japan back on its feet after the world went to crap?
You really shouldn't keep them waiting.
Wait a minute. Isn't your last name, Hiiragi?
Ah, you've finally figured out my secrets. I'm not just a sergeant. I'm basically royalty.
Now, feel free to worship me as much as you'd like.
Okay, okay, all joking aside, the Hiiragis can be an extremely intense group of people. So be careful, okay, Yu?
Do you?
There's my favorite moron.
So the most powerful family in Japan pages you and you come running like a dog.
What? Am I just supposed to ignore them then?
I've got a little story for you.
Once upon a time, a wise old man freed a doomed crane from a hunter's trap.
In return, the crane wove a beautiful cloth from its own wings as a gift for the man.
Huh? What are you talking about?
I am the wise man who saved you, remember?
And I was nice enough to teach you how to survive in this world and protect your family.
What's gotten into you? And why do I feel like you're patronizing me?
In a manner of speaking, you can return the favor today.
Will you just tell me what it is you want me-
I saved your life and now I own you. So don't go wagging your tail for them.
So that's what this is about. You don't control me.
You're wrong about that, Yu.
This is ridiculous. I don't care about whatever grudge you have against the Hiragi family.
It doesn't-
Shut up and listen, kid. You may not care about army politics, but that's the way this world works.
You don't have to worry about me, Gurren.
Come on. I'm not someone who abandons his friends. Haven't you learned that about me yet?
Yeah, I guess. But that doesn't make me feel any better. After all, I am not your friend.
Oh yeah? Well then what are you?
Guardian. You're superior. Lifesaver. I'm basically your god.
Ugh. Please.
What's up? Did you get called in too?
How did it go?
It was just a stupid interview.
Apparently I'm moving up a rank for my part in fighting off the vampires and my bravery on the battlefield.
A promotion, huh? Nice.
It's no surprise. I totally deserve it, don't you think?
If you say so.
Hey, wait! You can't just say that and then leave!
You know I shouldn't be promoted. I was completely useless when things got tough on the battlefield.
Sure, I can talk a big game, but I can't follow through.
It's because I'm... I'm so weak.
And yet, I bet I'm the only one getting promoted. Just because I'm part of the Sangu family.
Go ahead and laugh! Go on!
I'm a failure!
Stop it. I'm not laughing, Mitsuba.
It's weird. I mean, you and Shinoa? I had no idea until today that we basically have two princesses on our team.
Between the Sangus and the Hiragis, shouldn't we be living in a castle?
You are... such an idiot.
Whatever.
Anyway, this promotion is good news. The higher you go, the more you can help me out.
You mean, your family, right?
Yeah.
They're going to ask about that in the interview.
They think you might be a spy, so I've been ordered to keep an eye on you.
Oh? Wow. Do you think that I'm a spy?
I told them that was impossible, and that in my opinion, you're not smart enough to be a double agent. So there.
Thanks, I guess. But seriously, I'm glad that you believe in me.
Wait, you...
Hmm?
The Hiragi family is terrifying. Watch yourself.
I will. Thanks.
Was that a sigh? What do you have to be depressed about?
Shinoa, what are you doing out here?
Oh, nothing.
Just out enjoying a little walk.
Did the Hiragi family talk to you?
Yeah, they gave me a promotion.
I'm now a special second lieutenant.
Oh.
Wow, that's super impressive, Mitsu. And so shocking that a Sangu can get promoted without actually working for it.
Oh, don't be upset.
Oh, yeah?
What about you? I bet they were falling all over themselves to move you up a rank and make themselves even more-
No promotion here. And besides, if they did try to move me up a rank, I would just kindly refuse.
That sounds about right. The Hiragi's do what they want.
Not all of us. Actually, I kinda think my family has lost all hope for me these days.
Sure.
So, how much information did you have to give up in exchange for the promotion?
What do you mean?
They wanted to know about what happened when you freaked out, right? When he lost control?
I told them that I didn't know anything. Seemed like they didn't either.
If that's true, then the experimentation on you must not have been officially sanctioned by the Demon Army.
Do you have any idea what that was on the battlefield?
I don't. I wish I did.
In a world like this, it's not always clear who's on your side and who's not.
I just hope you's smart enough to know the difference.
What the...
Huh? But how did a vampire get in here?
Huh?
Geez, what kind of crap are they trying to pull?
That was a test of loyalty to make sure you aren't a traitor.
Now, shall we go ahead and start your interview?
Who the heck are you?
Kureto Hiragi, Imperial Demon Army Lieutenant General.
Yurichiro Hyakuya, let's get a better sense of how skilled you are with a sword.
But don't activate the curse.
Sounds like fun.
But don't get angry if I humiliate the almighty Hiragi.
Oh, you.
Perhaps it would be better if you don't listen to everything Brother Kureto says.
What?
Ignore him.
Possess me, Raimeki.
So this is the best you can do?
I have to admit I'm not impressed.
That was dirty.
Complain about someone fighting dirty in a real battle and see if that keeps them from killing you.
You do take orders well, at least.
You didn't even hesitate to follow my command.
Hard to believe you're that disobedient girl.
Back off.
Well, look at that.
You'd be dead right now if your comrade hadn't stepped in.
What?
Why the long face?
You don't think it was a dirty move for me to attack from behind, do you?
Huh.
I take back what I was going to say.
You are indeed Gurren's subordinate.
We're done?
That was pretty fast.
Xinyan.
Aw, but I don't wanna.
This isn't my kind of thing.
I don't enjoy bullying the weak.
As an adoptive son, you will do as you're told.
Man.
Well, if I must, fine.
Stop fooling around!
Who are you calling weak?
Why you, silly boy?
Wanna try me?
Well, that is the order I'm supposed to follow.
Let's begin.
After him.
Byakomaru.
Bang.
Bang!
That's it.
It's over.
And I'm not even that good at close combat compared to Kuroito or Gurren.
My Byakomaru is more of a long-range specialty weapon.
You do understand what that means about your skill level, yes?
yes but it's not your fault seems to me like you weren't properly trained to use your cursed gear
what a shame but try not to feel too pathetic
so then does that finally clear me of any suspicion it's obvious he doesn't know me
or my fighting style okay wait what the hell was that test really about they actually think that
i might be a traitor too since i'm friends with gurren crazy right it does seem there's a vampire
spy in the army somewhere though for the huragis that's a huge problem that must be dealt with
immediately then leave me out of it because if you think i'm the spy then you're out of bring him
along let go of me
kimizuki yo ichi
all right what have you done to them i interrogated them because we think you're the spy
you're insane let's start your interview you will speak only the truth deceive us and your friends
will die there isn't much background here in your file and yet you managed to somehow attain a black
demon weapon as did your two teammates over there normally there are thorough background checks
conducted for anyone going through the cursed gear ceremony but there weren't any for you three
why not where did the three of you come from what is your mission my mission i told you
do it stop it then answer truthfully i am i don't know what you want me to say the next one
stop i'll do whatever you want ask me anything good attitude let's talk more about your past
you grew up in the vampire city but you somehow managed to escape it was during your getaway that
the vampires brutally murdered your family which is why you're so hungry for revenge
at least that's what it says in the file is this correct yeah there's no way i'm working for those
blood suckers your protests aren't doing you any favors afterwards guren ichinose discovered you and
took you in the question is why why did guren take an interest in you what exactly are you to him
i don't is hyakuya really your last name or is that a lie too are you of the hyakuya sect
no i'm not it was just the name of the orphanage i grew up in are you aware that the hyakuya sect was
the largest spellcraft organization in japan they routinely brought lost children to their orphanage
and use them for human experimentation and to test out new forms of magic you were likely a lab rat for
spellcraft experimentation this is starting to make more sense guren must actually be trying to use
something the hyakuya sect put inside you come work for me instead you ichiro hyakuya allow me to be your new
guide
let yoichi and kimizuki go right now
we're all done here
i don't know what's up between you and guren or what you're fighting about
but at least guren wouldn't use this kind of torture
i know that's why i'm always one step ahead of him you're free to go now
what a messed up place this is but still i can't wait to see what you do next lab rat
you're so fidgety are you really that worried about you huh i don't know what you're talking
about i mean why would i worry about an idiot like him oh you
you whoa kamizuki and yoichi look terrible
what happened to you what's going on that interview was total crap the stupid hiragi
guren you better start explaining
kurito said that me my family all of us were used as guinea pigs experimented on by some weirdo
sect practicing spellcraft tell me the truth did you save me just so you could use me
that's right i don't have the luxury of saving anyone who doesn't serve a higher purpose
so what are you gonna start sulking now
no regardless of your reasons i would have died if you didn't find me
all i want to know is if i'm of use to you in our fight against the vampires
if i am then you must want to recruit mika as well right he was a lab rat too
i don't care about whatever the hyakuya did to me i can't change that
it's done just tell me how i can get mika back but you like i said before everyone here is your family
and that includes me that means we'll work together to get the rest of your family back
if that's true then teach me how to be a better fighter show me the proper way to use my cursed gear
why don't you take a little sip already
after all mika this is probably the best looking you're ever going to be
you wouldn't want to risk excuse me sorry but i heard that if i offer my blood to you
then you could make life easier for me and my family
who told you such a thing was it you
here mika come and taste this kid's blood quench your terrible thirst
it's against the rules to drink directly from a human you're such a goody two-shoes
or maybe you're just thinking of him you're scared that you what are you doing here ferret
ah right i came here to invite you to something you must attend the next progenitor council meeting
the progenitor council what do they want it'll be so much more interesting if you find out for
yourself megan dear now shall we go
you
it's so painful i need your help you
next time on serif of the end complicated connections